const english = {
  level1Eng: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'What is a colloquial?',
      selection: ['Informal spoken language', 'An exaggeration used for effect', 'An imitation of a sound they represent', 'A comparison of two things'],
      answer: 'Informal spoken language',
      description: 'Informal spoken language is used to give a conversational tone.'
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What is an example of a Personification?',
      selection: ['"Traffic slowed to a crawl."', '"The sun is bright and yellow."', '"The door went SLAM!"', '"The snow is a white blanket."'],
      answer: '"Traffic slowed to a crawl."',
      description: 'A Personification is the attribution of a personal nature or human characteristics to something non-human, or the representation of an abstract quality in human form.'
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What is a Euphemism?',
      selection: ['A way of emphasising a point.', 'A phrase that is less offensive or less troubling than another.', 'Language that makes fun of someone.', 'A direct request or command.'],
      answer: 'A phrase that is less offensive or less troubling than another.',
      description: 'A Euphemism is a mild or indirect word or expression substituted for one considered to be too harsh or blunt when referring to something unpleasant or embarrassing.'
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'What is third person viewpoint?',
      selection: ['Uses "I"', 'Uses "he, she"', 'An all seeing, all knowing narrator.', 'Uses "their, them"'],
      answer: 'Uses "he, she"',
      description: 'Third Person Viewpoint is when the narrator is not a character, therefore uses "he, she".'
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'What is the coreect term for an exaggeration used for effect?',
      selection: ['Repitition', 'Hyperbole', 'Anecdote', 'Pun'],
      answer: 'Hyperbole',
      description: 'A Hyperbole is an exaggerated statement or claim not meant to be taken literally (for effect).'
    }
  ],
  level2Eng: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    }
  ],
  level3Eng: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'What is an example of a Personification?',
      selection: ['"Traffic slowed to a crawl."', '"The sun is bright and yellow."', '"The door went SLAM!"', '"The snow is a white blanket."'],
      answer: '"Traffic slowed to a crawl."',
      description: 'A Personification is the attribution of a personal nature or human characteristics to something non-human, or the representation of an abstract quality in human form.'
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What is a Euphemism?',
      selection: ['A way of emphasising a point.', 'A phrase that is less offensive or less troubling than another.', 'Language that makes fun of someone.', 'A direct request or command.'],
      answer: 'A phrase that is less offensive or less troubling than another.',
      description: 'A Euphemism is a mild or indirect word or expression substituted for one considered to be too harsh or blunt when referring to something unpleasant or embarrassing.'
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: '',
      selection: ['', '', '', ''],
      answer: '',
      description: ''
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'What is third person viewpoint?',
      selection: ['Uses "I"', 'Uses "he, she"', 'An all seeing, all knowing narrator.', 'Uses "their, them"'],
      answer: 'Uses "he, she"',
      description: 'Third Person Viewpoint is when the narrator is not a character, therefore uses "he, she".'
    }
  ]
}

export default english
